We're going to have another great Superbowl folks.
Here's a little, nice little bite size focaccia wedges.
To top off, I'm just going to use my little dried marjoram.
Going to go over the top.
Gives it a nice little flavor.
Real nice Italian, also looks good for our garnish.
And I also have our fresh basil and our peppers that I'm just going to go over just a little bit with the freshness of this.
Alright, we're back.
This is the final product.
The crew, my camera girl said just don't eat any cause I want to get my final shot and I'm telling you, we're all waiting to dig in.
These are just that good.
The fresh pepper and the parsley make it.
Don't worry about the cold of the, you know, that's just going to make it that much better.
What you might want to do now is just drizzle a little bit of olive oil.
A little drizzle of olive oil over the whole top.
Very easy, not too much.
And that's it man.